（忆往昔）
迪恩 你刚刚是怎么回事
Dean, what was that all about back there?
易形者已经死了之后的那几枪
All those extra shots after the shifter was already dead.
你确定那不是…和血印有关
Sure it wasn't something to do with the mark?
不是 都不是
No, no. None of that.
我得说实话
Look, man, I gotta be honest.
我有点焦虑 我想要确保自己没做错什么
I was a little anxious. I wanted to make sure it was done right.
我为什么还要解释
Why am I even explaining this?
迪恩 我
Dean, I …
- 你怎么做到的 - 魔法
- How did you do it? - Magic.
我们是来找这个女巫的 罗威娜
We're here for the witch. Rowena.
能被认出来总是很高兴
Always nice to be recognized.
[咒语]
我们抓住了她
We got her.
该给我致命一击了
Time for the coup de grace.
你这是怎么了
Something the matter with you?
母亲
Mother?
我名叫吉米·诺瓦克
My name is Jimmy Novak.
来自伊利诺伊州的庞蒂亚克
I'm from Pontiac, Illinois.
有一个家庭 艾米莉娅和克莱尔
I have a family … Amelia and Claire.
感谢你赐予的食物 我们将无比珍惜你的恩赐
Bless this food and ourselves to thy loving service.
阿门
Amen.
爸爸
Hi, daddy.
你占据了个可怜虫的身体
You're possessing some poor bastard?
卡西迪奥 你答应过我 我家人会没事
Castiel! You promised me my family would be okay!
那些我们为了任务而牺牲的人类呢
What of the humans whose lives we sacrifice?
也许现在该把他们摆在第一位了
Maybe it's time to put them first.
（如今）
（伊利诺伊州 庞蒂亚克）
别碰我 你个变态
Get your hands off me, perv.
否则我告你
I'll sue your ass.
这次又怎么了
What was it this time?
商店盗窃 那人不打算提出指控
Shoplifting. The guy ain't lookin' to press charges,
但我想你大概会想要她回来
but I figured you'd want her back.
你要关48小时禁闭
That's 48 hours in isolation.
好怕怕
Scary.
这姑娘是谁
Who is this girl?
经常出走的孩子之一
One of our frequent flyers.
克莱尔·诺瓦克
Claire Novak.
诺瓦克 你有访客
Novak, you got a visitor.
真的吗
Really?
你爸爸来见你了
Your father's here to see you.
爸爸
Daddy?
我不是你父亲
I am not your father.
你好 克莱尔
Hello, Claire.
好久不见
It's been a long time.
[邪恶力量 第10季第9集]
能让我们单独谈谈吗
Can we have a moment?
我就在外面
I'll be outside.
我不是你父亲
I'm not your father.
是啊
Right.
「我不是你父亲」
"I'm not your father."
那是你对我说的第一句话 记得吗
Those were the first words you ever said to me. Remember?
我什么都记得
I remember everything.
我也是 卡西迪奥
So do I, Castiel.
我爸爸
My dad…
他还在你身体里吗
Is he still in there?
不
No.
人的灵魂 只能占据一具
The human soul, it can only occupy a body.
具有一定结构完整性的躯体
while it retains a certain… structural integrity.
这具皮囊…
and this vessel, it was…
曾被一个大天使粉碎到亚原子级
it was ripped apart on a subatomic level by an archangel.
那你怎么…
Well, then how are you…
我被重新组装到一起了
I was reassembled.
你父亲上天堂了
Your father is in heaven.
那恭喜他
Well, yay for him.
总之 聊得很愉快 滚出我的生活吧
Anyway, good talk. You can get the hell out of my life now.
- 克莱尔 - 干什么
- Claire… - What?
干什么
What?
你已经夺走了我的一切 你还想怎么样
You took everything from me. What do you want now?
没什么 我就是…
Nothing. I just…
我是来帮你的
I came here to help you.
为什么
Why?
因为我给了你太多伤害
Because I've hurt you so much.
你妈妈在哪
Where's your mother?
你走后几个月
About a few months after you,
她跑了
she took off.
把我丢在了奶奶家 去「寻找自我」了
Dropped me off at my grandma's and went to go "find herself."
看来她还没找到呢
I guess she's still looking.
你被关在了…
And you're in a…
儿童监狱里吗
Child prison?
这是教养院
It's a group home.
奶奶死后 我没有别的亲人了
After my gran died, I didn't have anyone, so…
于是就在各种寄养家庭
Bounced around to different foster families,
和这种地方辗转
places like this.
简直梦想成真
Living the dream, you know?
克莱尔 对不起
Well, Claire, I'm sorry, and…
我永远无法替代我夺去的东西
I can never replace what I took from you,
但如果你需要什么 任何事
but if there is anything you need, anything at all…
把我弄出去
Get me out of here.
怎么做
How?
你有领带吗
Do you own a tie?
别摆弄了
Stop it.
好了
There.
这下你有当爹的样子了
Now you look like a dad.
不用客气
No, no.
好了
So…
诺瓦克先生
Mr. Novak,
我听说你想得到你女儿的监护权
I understand you want custody of your daughter.
是的
Yes, that's, uh, that's…
没错
That's right.
为什么
Why?
什么
Excuse me?
这个问题很简单
It's a simple question.
你消失了好几年
You vanish for years.
不联络 圣诞节都不寄贺卡
No contact, not even a christmas card.
为什么现在回来了
Why come back now?
我…我没有…
I, um… I didn't, uh…
- 我一直在外旅行 - 公差
- I was traveling. - For work.
公差 没错
Work. Yes.
去了好久啊
Long trip.
你是做什么的
And what is it that you do exactly?
我…
I…um…
我对抗一些对人类致命的威胁
I fight certain deadly threats to humanity.
- 他是个除虫员 - 我是除虫员
- He's an exterminator. - I'm an exterminator.
我好像有臭虫呢
You know, I think I might have bedbugs.
能给点建议吗
Any tips?
当然
Of course.
好好睡 别被臭虫咬了
You should sleep tight and not let them bite.
我会试试的
I'll try that.
这无所谓
It doesn't matter.
他是我爸爸
He's my dad,
他想带我走 我就可以走
and he wants to sign me out, so I'm out.
这是法律 桑迪
That's the law, Sandy.
克莱尔 去走廊等我
Claire, wait for me in the hallway.
- 你不能… - 快去
- You can't… - Now.
我不喜欢骗子 诺瓦克先生
I don't do well with liars, Mr. Novak.
- 但是… - 省省吧
- But… - Save it.
我要拒绝你的监护权申请
I'm denying your application for custody.
我不是想唱白脸 真的
I'm not trying to be the bad guy here. I'm not.
但克莱尔成年之前 她都归我管
But until Claire turns 18, she is my responsibility.
我知道你是想做你认为正确的事
I know you're trying to do what you think is best.
我知道你想做她的朋友
I know you wanna be her friend.
是啊
I do.
问题就在这里 诺瓦克先生
And that's our problem, Mr. Novak.
克莱尔有问题
Claire's troubled.
这几年她过得不容易
The last few years have not been easy for her.
她需要的不是朋友 而是父亲
And she doesn't need a friend. She needs a father.
小心点
Easy now.
笑什么呢
What are you laughing at?
等等
Hang on.
看看 这太经典了
It's a… this is a classic.
很高兴你感觉好些了
I'm glad you're feeling better.
好极了
Oh, yeah, better than ever.
你好啊 美人
Hello, beautiful.
好棒
Oh, yeah.
需要跟它独处一会儿吗
You want some alone time with that thing?
不用 等等
No, no. Wait.
- 真的 - 嗯 看啊
- You sure? - Yeah. Yeah. Watch this.
不 别啊
No. Don't be…
站住
Hey, stop!
Stop!
是你啊
It's you.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我要带你出去
I'm getting you out of here.
他…
Is he…
睡着了
He's sleeping.
坐下
Sit.
别动
Stay.
乖狗狗
Good dog.
等等
Wait!
我儿子
My son…
我要跟他说话
I need to talk to him.
都好几周了
It's been weeks.
跟他说 我很对不起
Tell him I'm sorry.
告诉他
Tell him…
怎么了
Yeah?
没事
Nothing.
你该吃点蔬菜什么的
It's just…you could eat a vegetable.
番茄酱就是蔬菜
Ketchup's a vegetable.
你变了
You've changed.
我认识的那个卡西迪奥
The Castiel I met?
不是个东西
He was crappy.
又拽又混蛋
Like, super stuck-up and a dick.
让人想一拳打在他的天使脸上
and you just wanted to punch him in his stupid angel face.
我觉得我还不至于吧
I don't think I was that bad.
绝对有
You totally were.
你现在
And now you're just…
怎么说呢 待人亲多了
I don't know. Nicer.
有点呆 别介意
And kind of a doof. No offense.
嗯
Yes. Well, um…
我之前的确很自以为是
Before, I was very self-assured.
我坚信自己走的是正义之道
I was convinced I was on this righteous path.
现在我知道根本没有这回事
Now I realize that there is no righteous path,
人只能在一个太容易
just people trying to do their best.
堕落的世界里 尽力而为
in a world where it's far too easy to do your worst.
好深刻
Deep.
是啊 对呆子来说还不错了
Yeah. For a doof.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们接下来去哪
So…where do we go next?
多谢你请我吃饭
Look… I appreciate the meal.
并犯下重罪解救我
And, you know, the felony.
但你不用给我当保姆
But you don't need to babysit me.
我能照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你觉得愧疚 所以救我出来
I mean you felt guilty, so you busted me out.
谢了 但我们两清了
So thanks, but we're good.
谁也不欠谁
Even Steven.
不 我们犯了罪
No, we, um, we committed a crime.
你可能还会需要我
And you might need me again,
所以我们还是待在一起吧
so I think we should stick together.
好吧
Okay.
要买点东西上路吗
You wanna get some stuff for the road, huh?
我得去尿尿
I have to pee.
好的
Uh, oh, okay.
- 抱歉 - 怪我
- I'm sorry. - My bad.
（青少年杂志）
给小姑娘买的
It's for a teenage girl.
她去上厕所了
She's urinating.
我的钱包没了
My wallet's gone.
帮帮忙 该死
Hey, can you help? Damn.
帮帮忙 拜托了
Help! Please?
- 克莱尔 - 谢谢
- Claire. - Thanks.
快走
Go, go, go, go!
等等 克莱尔
Wait! Hey! Claire!
你就为这事找我们 这就是你的「急事」
This is why you called us? This is your emergency?
是啊
Yes.
不 小卡
No, Cass.
有人死了才叫急事呢
An emergency is a dead body, okay?
或者天使发狂
Or… or… or a wigged out angel.
或者天启第三次卷土重来
or the apocalypse, take 3.
有个小丫头从你眼皮底下跑了这不叫急事
Some chick bolting on you is not an emergency. That's…
萨姆每周五晚上都能遇到
That's every Friday night for Sam.
- 喂喂 - 就是嘛
- Dude. - Well…
她不是什么小丫头
This isn't just some chick.
我要对她负责的
I'm responsible for her.
为什么啊 你多少年前见过她一面来着
Since when? You met her once… how many years ago?
小卡 就算我们找到了克莱尔 然后呢
Look, Cass, even if we do find Claire, then what?
她抢了你 然后跑了
She rolled you and then she ran, okay?
她显然不想跟你过家家
It's pretty clear that she doesn't wanna play house.
我明白
I understand,
但我得确保克莱尔的安全
but I need to know that Claire is safe,
我需要你们帮忙
and I need your help.
好吧
All right.
我们去教养院打听一下吧
Why don't we go ask around at the group home?
这样吧
Uh, you know what?
我们留下 以防她回来
We're gonna stick here in case she circles back.
你去吧
You go ahead.
谢了
Thank you.
番茄酱是蔬菜吗
Is ketchup a vegetable?
必须是啊
Hell, yes.
说吧 为什么要搞家人团聚这一出
All right, so spill. What's with the family reunion?
说不清
I don't know.
我一直在想人
Just been… thinking about people.
你吃吧
No problem.
我帮过一些人 但也伤害了一些人
I've helped some, but I've… I've hurt some.
你是中年危机了呗
So you're having a midlife crisis.
我很老了 我觉得我有这权利
Well, I'm extremely old. I think I'm entitled.
小卡 听我说
Cass, listen to me.
有些事你必须放下
There's some stuff you just gotta let go.
好吗
Okay?
你辜负的人 你没能救下的人
The people you let down, the ones you can't save…
只能忘了他们 这是为了你好
You gotta forget about 'em, for your own good.
你就这么做吗
Is that what you do?
我完全不这么做 但是…
That's the opposite of what I do. But…
我可不是什么好榜样
I ain't exactly a role model.
不是这样的
That's not true.
少来了
Yeah.
你还好吗 迪恩
How are you, Dean?
好啊
Fine.
我很好
I'm great.
才不是
No, you're not.
我没有黑眼了 这是好事
Yeah, well, I've lost the black eyes, so that's a plus.
但我还有这个
But I still have this.
该隐血印对你还有影响吗
The Mark of Cain still affecting you?
迪恩
Dean?
小卡 答应我一件事
Cass, I need you to promise me something.
当然
Of course.
如果我真投入了黑暗 你得干掉我
If I do go dark side, you gotta take me out.
什么意思
What do you mean?
捅我 灭我 把我丢进太阳
Knife me, smite me, throw me into the freakin' sun.
随你
Whatever.
别让萨姆拦你 他肯定要试的
And don't let Sam get in the way, because he'll try.
我不能再走那条路了
I can't go down that road again, man.
我不能再成为恶魔了
I can't be that thing again.
不会管用的
That won't work.
又没问你 勇敢的心
I didn't ask you, braveheart.
自由
Freedom!
你为什么被关了进来
So…what are we in for?
就是唠唠嗑
Small talk, darling.
消磨时光
Just passing the time.
我在这儿是因为我不该在这儿
I'm here because I shouldn't be here.
那是谜语吗
Is that a riddle?
克劳力只允许一部分恶魔上地面
Crowley only allows certain demons to come earth-side.
我不在获批名单上 所以自己想办法溜了出来
I wasn't on the list, so I had to get myself smuggled up.
- 你拿什么交换的 - 做件事
- And what did that cost? - A favor.
- 大事吗 - 很血腥
- Big? - Bloody.
我猜大王会让我关一阵
Now…I figure the king lets me stew for a while,
然后就会来审问我怎么逃出地狱的
then he starts asking how I Houdini'd hell.
而且他不会客气的
And he ain't gonna ask nice.
你呢
What about you?
你干了什么
What's your sin?
我是个糟糕透顶的母亲
I was a horrible mother.
她是个糟糕透顶的母亲
She was a horrible mother.
我跟没跟你提过
Did I tell you the time that.
她差点拿我去换3头猪的事
she almost traded me for three pigs?
3头啊 我小时候很可爱呢
Three! I was an attractive child.
还会杂耍
I could juggle.
至少也值5头猪
I was worth five pigs at least.
我妈妈会拿烟头烫我
My ma used to burn me with cigarettes.
没人在乎 杰拉德
Nobody cares, Gerald.
更别提名字了
Don't get me started about the name.
费格斯
"Fergus."
听着像性病
It sounds like a venereal disease,
还是很讨厌的那种
and not the fun kind.
老大
Look, boss,
如果你这么讨厌这女人
if you hate this Betty so much,
为什么不杀了她
why not end her?
我自有原因
I've my reasons.
我就杀了我妈
Oh, I killed my old lady.
因为她拿烟头烫我
Because of the cigarettes.
我乐意杀了你妈
I have no problem doing yours.
克莱尔是个好孩子 警探 很聪明
Claire's a good kid, detective. She's smart.
而且 她其实很善良
And underneath it all, she has a big heart.
这里以前有个男孩
You know, there used to be a boy here.
达斯汀·塔特
Dustin Tate.
他年长一些 但克莱尔很照顾他
He was older, but Claire really took him under her wing.
他还在吗
Is he around?
他在香肠屋工作
He works at the Wiener Hut.
我们也想给克莱尔找家 但她总逃跑
We tried to place Claire, but she always ran away.
有时候逃走几天 有次逃了半年
Sometimes for a couple of days, one time for six months.
她待在哪
Where did she hide out?
不知道
Wish I knew.
克莱尔
Hey, Claire.
兰迪在吗
Is, uh, Randy here?
瞧瞧谁回来了
Oh. Look who's back.
都多久了 3天
It's been…what? Three days?
是啊 我被抓了
I know. I got busted.
但我带来了礼物
But I come bearing gifts.
这里面有两百多呢
There's, like, 200 bucks in there.
（詹姆斯·诺瓦克）
詹姆斯·诺瓦克
James Novak.
你亲戚吗
Any relation?
不是 就是个路人
No. He's just a guy.
多谢帮忙 不过
Well… I appreciate the elbow grease, but, uh,
还是不够
we're still short.
还差多少
How much?
很多
Too much.
萨林杰什么时候来收钱
When's Salinger coming to collect?
今晚
Tonight.
都怪我
It's my fault.
我不该借那么多钱
I shouldn't have borrowed so much money.
但是 圣诞要到了
But, uh, the holidays are coming,
我想给孩子们买点好东西
and I like to spoil my kids.
或许他会再宽限些时间
Maybe he'll give us some more time.
他是放高利贷的 那种人不会给你第二次机会
He's a loan shark. They're not so big on second chances.
我还以为
Kinda thought you were gonna…
你会像我们说好的那样 偷到足够的钱还债
Steal enough to pay down the debt, like we talked about.
但是…
But, uh…
我尽力了
I tried.
还不够努力
Not hard enough.
好了
Come on.
最后一顿家庭晚餐
One last family meal.
我们肯定还有办法的
There's gotta be something we can do.
怎么了
What?
没事 太疯狂了
It's nothin'. It's crazy.
如果我还未成年 我就去做了
I'd do it if I was still under 18.
说吧
Tell me.
（香肠屋）
达斯汀·塔特
Dustin Tate?
不是
Nah, man.
是吗
Oh, really?
你就是
Yes, you are.
告诉我克莱尔·诺瓦克在哪
And you're gonna tell me where Claire Novak is.
马上
Now.
你还是听他的吧
I'd do what he says.
快进快出
Quick in, quick out.
小心摄像头
Watch out for the cameras.
小心
Be careful.
等到只剩下你
Wait till you're alone,
然后狠狠收拾那个收银员
then you hit that register jockey hard.
让他吓破胆 懂吗
Put the fear of god in him. You understand?
很好
Good.
然后回到我身边来
You come back to me, you hear?
你和达斯汀 你们是我仅有的家人
You and Dustin… you're the only family I got.
我们走了
Excuse us.
- 克莱尔 等等 - 去你的
- Claire, wait! - Screw you.
别激动啊 小刺头
Hey, Miley Cyrus, settle.
去死吧 老头子
Eat me, Hasselhoff.
克莱尔 别激动
Claire, hold on a second.
- 我叫… - 萨姆
- Look, my name's… - Sam.
你是迪恩
And you're Dean.
我们见过的 记得吗
We've met, remember?
克莱尔
Claire.
你刚刚是打算去打劫那个便利店吗
You were going to rob that convenience store?
那又怎样
So?
这样…
So…it's…
是不对的
wrong.
你想对我说教是与非吗
You wanna talk to me about wrong?
你杀了我爸爸
You killed my dad.
这对你而言算是滔天大错了吗
Is that wrong enough for you?
- 不 我没杀他 - 真的吗
- No, I didn't. - Really?
因为要不是你 他就还会在这里
Because without you, he'd still be here,
我妈妈也还会在
and my mom would still be around.
克莱尔 我…
Claire, I'm…
别过来
Don't.
那伤不了我的
That won't hurt me.
好吧
Fine.
- 拜托 - 等等
- Hey, come on. - Hold on a second.
为什么
Why?
这难道不是你们自找的吗
Like you don't have it coming?
这个怪物占据了我爸 你们却袖手旁观
You stood there while this monster took my dad.
我曾经向你祷告 卡西迪奥
I used to pray to you, Castiel.
每天晚上
Every night.
我祈求你把他安全地带回家
I would beg you to bring him home safe.
我知道
I know.
你知道…
You know…
我爸爸是个好人
My father was a good man.
这世界多么黑白颠倒
In what messed up world.
他就得死 而你却能活下来
does he have to die and you get to live?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
不 你只是觉得愧疚
No. You feel guilty.
这两者是不一样的
There's a difference.
怎么 你要跑回兰迪那里
So what, now you run back to Randy,
跑回指使你偷东西的人那里
the guy you steal for?
- 你怎么知道的 - 达斯汀
- How do you know about that? - Dustin.
克莱尔
Claire.
那男人在利用你
That man is using you.
他保护了我
He was there for me.
当情况变坏的时候 急转直下的时候
When things got bad … and they got real damn bad …
除了他没有别人帮我
he was there when no one else was.
他是我的家人
He's my family,
而你只不过是…
and you're just…
你下地狱吧
You can go to hell.
老大要见你
Boss will see you now.
母亲
Mother.
费格斯
Fergus.
是克劳力
Crowley.
费格斯
Fergus.
你没变
So you haven't changed.
但你却绝对变了
But you certainly have.
地狱之王 厉害啊
King of Hell. Bravo.
我一直知道我儿子注定要成大事
I always knew my boy was meant for big things.
真的吗
Really?
我可记得
As I remember it,
你说过我会死在哪个阴沟里
you said I would die in a gutter,
淹没在我自己的呕吐物里
covered in my own sick.
我是在激励你做得更好点
I was motivating you to do better.
目标更高远一点
Aim higher.
而且显然 这起作用了
And clearly, it worked.
你是怎么死的
How did you die?
重点是
The point is,
你恨我
you hated me.
得了
Oh, please.
你说 你马上就回来
You said you'd be back in a flash,
然后你就消失了
and then you disappeared!
我当时才8岁 8岁
I was 8 years old! 8!
别闹了
Oh, now you're being dramatic.
- 我都没有爸爸 - 你当然有爸爸
- I didn't even have a father! - Of course you had a father.
我是在一次冬至群交中怀上你的
You were just conceived during a winter solstice orgy.
我又不会问对方名字
And it's not like I was taking names.
你想让我说什么 我…
What do you want me to say? I…
我跟当地人起了点争执
I had a…disagreement with the locals. And.
他们放出猎犬追我 我当然得跑
when they set their hounds on me, I had to leave.
跑了就不回来了 跑了几百年
And never come back? For hundreds of years?
可我现在来了
But I'm here now.
我们还有机会
We have a second chance.
我们可以再次成为一家人 费格斯
We can be a real family again, Fergus.
我叫克劳力
Crowley.
而且我有家人
And I have a family.
谁 恶魔吗
Who? The demons?
他们如果觉得能得逞
Any one of them would stab you in the back.
都会毫不犹豫地出卖你
if they thought they could get away with it.
你就不会吗
And you wouldn't?
不会 我们是一家人 我们血脉相连
No! Because we're family! We're blood!
你可以相信我
You can trust me,
我能帮你
And I can help you.
我明白你很愤怒
I understand you're angry.
我明白你…
I understand that you…
恨我
hate me.
如果你想继续锁着我
And if you want to keep me locked away,
没问题
then so be it.
但要知道 我永远是你妈妈
But know that I'll always be your mother.
我会永远爱你
And I'll always love you.
给我来…
Give me a shot of, um…
三杯威士忌
Three whiskeys.
小卡 别太责备自己
Cass, don't beat yourself up, man.
克莱尔…
Claire was…
是对的
Right.
她是对的
She was right.
我有什么资格教她怎么生活
Who am I to tell her how to live her life?
总得有人教她
Well, somebody needs to.
她可不是什么特雷莎修女
It's not like we're talking about mother Teresa here.
那姑娘差点去抢便利店
The girl just about knocked over a gas 'n sip.
- 她有问题 - 是我造成的
- She's got issues. - Because of me.
你还穿着她老爸的肉身呢
Well, you are wearing her old man's meatsuit.
或许只能火上浇油
Probably didn't help.
我以为我能弥补她
I thought I could make it up to her.
我觉得你弥补不了
I don't think you can.
吉米是她父亲 对某些人来说
I mean, Jimmy was her father. And to some people, that's…
那就是一切 你明白吗
that's everything, you know?
不 我不明白 我并不了解我父亲
No. I don't. I never knew my father.
至少可以说 他一直很疏远
He was distant, to say the least.
你们呢 你们爱你们的父亲吗
What about you? Did you love your father?
全心全意
With everything I had.
没错
Yeah.
有时很不容易 但我们爱他
Yeah, I mean, it wasn't always easy, but yeah.
约翰·温彻斯特绝对算不上
I mean, look, John Winchester's not gonna win.
「最佳老爸」 好吧 但…
any "Number one dad" awards, you know? But…
我们有需要的时候 他都在
You know, damn if he wasn't there when we needed him.
跟他说说纽约那次
Tell him about that time in New York.
哦对了
Oh, yeah.
好吧 是这样
Yeah, okay. So, um…
当时我们在长岛猎魔
We were working this haunting in long island,
然后我和萨姆恳求老爸
and … and me and sam begged the old man.
让我们进一次城
to let us go to the city for once.
他对纽约有点偏见
He had this thing about New York, right?
觉得那里太大 太吵 太脏了
Too big, too loud, too dirty.
- 而且他讨厌洋基队 - 超级讨厌 没错
- Yeah, and he hated the yankees. - Big-time. Yeah.
总之 我们说服了他让我们去
Somehow, we convinced him to let us go.
然后我们都去了 到处逛景点
So we all go. We all, you know, see all the sights,
坐了地铁 吃了很多披萨
and, uh, ride the subway, eat too much pizza,
全玩了个遍
the whole nine.
到了半夜 萨姆和爸都精疲力尽了
Well, by about midnight, Sam and dad are zonked,
我想 管他的
and I figure, screw it.
我要去摇滚俱乐部
I'm going to CBGB.
- CBGB是… - 我知道
- So CBGB is … I know.
雷蒙斯乐队和金发美女乐队就是在那儿起家的
It's where the Ramones and Blondie got their start.
没错
Right.
总之
Well, anyways,
那时候他年龄还远远不到能进酒吧
he was way underage at the time.
我去了
Yeah, so I get there.
溜了进去 那里简直是疯了
I sneak in, and it is nuts.
人人都喝得醉醺醺的 吞云吐雾
I mean, people are drinking and they're smoking.
不知在吸食什么东西
and they're … they're snortin' whatever.
有个顶着莫霍克头的大块头在台上咆哮
There's a 500-pound guy on stage with a Mohawk just screamin'.
我的脑子快爆炸了 根本不知道该怎么做
And, uh, my mind is blown. I don't even know what to do.
然后一个女孩走过来对我说
Then this girl walks up and she says,
「好啊 来我们桌坐坐
"Hey, why don't you come over and sit down.
跟我的朋友聊聊天吧「
with my friends at our table?"
- 我说好 - 对
- All right. - Yeah,
然后他们把他灌醉了 第一次
and they get him drunk. First time.
但那感觉可不好受
But not fun drunk.
我不确定他们往酒里放了什么东西
I'm not quite sure what was in that stuff.
整个房间都转了起来
But the room starts to spin.
我觉得我要吐了 一直吐下去
And I feel like I'm gonna puke. Forever.
就在那时
And right about that time,
我听到了他叫我
I hear him.
「迪恩·温切斯特」
"Dean Winchester!"
我老爹
My old man.
我不知道他怎么做到的 他找到了我
I don't know how, but he found me.
我完全吓坏了
And now I'm really freaking out,
因为他就那么站在那里 一言不发
'cause he's just standing there, not saying anything.
我看看周围 所有人都吓坏了
I look around. Everybody else is freaking out, too.
没人敢直视他的眼睛
In fact, nobody's even looking him in the eye.
最后 一个鼻子里穿了根安全别针
And finally, this one guy with, like, a safety pin through his nose.
身上纹了「挡我者死」的男人抬起头
and a-a "Kill everything" tattoo looks up,
对他说「对不起 先生」
and he says, "Sorry, sir."
「对不起 先生」
Yeah. Sorry, sir.
对约翰·吓死人·温切斯特说
To John Friggin' Winchester.
他救了你
He saved you.
对 可你知道我怎么回报他的吗
Yeah. And you know what he got for that?
我埋怨他让我当众丢人
Me whining about how much he embarrassed me.
我对他说我恨他
Me telling him that I hate him.
他站住了 转过身来
But then he stopped, he turned around.
看着我说
and he looked at me and he said,
「儿子 你不喜欢我 没关系
"Son, you don't like me? That's fine.
做爸爸的不一定要你喜欢「
It's not my job to be liked.
「但我要把你好好养大」
"It's my job to raise you right."
是啊 他做到了
Yeah. And he did.
你们觉得克莱尔会不会有麻烦了
You think Claire is in trouble?
她跟一个叫兰迪的人在一起
She's hanging out with a guy named Randy.
- 必须有麻烦 - 马上来
- She's in trouble. - Coming right up.
兰迪
Randy.
晚上好 小姐
Evenin', little lady.
亲爱的
Honey?
你带了什么东西给我吗
You have something for me?
不
No!
亮枪
Guns blazing, huh?
这就是你的计划吗
That was your plan?
相信我
Trust me.
这烂人 不值得你这样做
This pile of crap? He ain't worth it.
把她关到别的房间去
Put her in the other room.
她有股狠劲 我喜欢
She's got fight. I like that.
上一个往我脸上吐唾沫的妹子 我娶了她
I married the last girl that spit in my face.
过去几个月
Last few months,
你赌马输了很多
you've lost a bundle on the ponies.
你现在欠我多少钱
How much you owe me now?
5000美元
$5, 000.
不如 我饶你一马
So how about I give you a break?
你把那姑娘给我
And you give me the girl.
你开玩笑呢吧
That's a joke, right?
克莱尔对我来说就像家人
Claire's like family to me.
得了 我了解这骗术 好吗
Please. I know the con, all right?
你找一个有恋父情结的孩子
You find some kid with major league daddy issues,
然后让她为你偷窃
and then you get her to steal for you.
别装骄傲的父亲了
Cut the proud papa act.
我给你个好价码
I'll make you a good deal.
我说了
Like I said,
克莱尔是我的家人
Claire's family.
所以你的价码得够好
So it better be a damn good deal.
过来
Come on!
住手
Stop!
我知道是谁在往地面偷运灵魂
I know who's been smuggling souls up from hell.
真的吗 快说吧
Really? Pray do tell.
他
Him.
什么
What?
是真的 先生 大人
It … it's true, mister… Uh, my lord.
杰拉德他…我们做了交易
Gerald, he… we made a deal.
她说谎
She's lying.
为什么 她为什么要说谎
Why? Why would she lie?
够了 杰拉德
That's enough of that, Gerald.
我要杀了你 贱人
I'll kill you, bitch!
够了 杰拉德
That's enough, Gerald.
快死吧
Come on.
我说了够了 杰拉德
I said that's enough, Gerald.
谢谢
Thank you.
来吗
Coming?
罗威娜
Rowena.
你说过如果我撒谎 你就会把我救出去
You said that if I lied, you'd get me out of here.
我会的 亲爱的
Oh, and I will, darling.
我马上就回来
I'll be back in a flash.
你叫克莱尔 对吧
It's Claire, right?
你真的很漂亮 你知道吗
You really are a pretty one, you know that?
别动
Don't.
别过来
Back it up.
那女孩在哪里
Where's the girl?
不 不
Aah! No! No!
克莱尔
Claire.
克莱尔 克莱尔
Claire. Claire!
兰迪
Randy.
带她离开这里
Get her outta here.
对 走吧
Yeah. Go.
走吧
Go.
别过来
Hey, back up!
Back up!
别犯傻
Don't be as dumb as you look.
你们不会想这么做的
You guys don't wanna do this.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean.
告诉我你是没别的办法
Tell me you had to do this.
我…
I-I did…
- 我不是有意的 - 不
- I didn't mean to. - No.
告诉我 是因为他们还是你
Tell me it was them or you!